<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<notes xmlns="http://localhost/tapas" xmlns:tei="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <note xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" id="note_001" place="bottom">
      <hi id="idp659792" style="vertical-align: super;">*</hi> So he wrote in 1855, but a few years
                    after he gave the sword to a friend for whom he had a great affection, who carried it back to
                    America as a token" of good-will and sympathy. This friend was Bayard Taylor, a true knight, and
                    worthy to carry the honorable bloodless weapon.</note>
   <note xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" style="; " id="note_002">
      <hi id="idp701536" style="vertical-align: super;">*</hi> 
                    Some one has given me a map of Kensington in 1764, by which
                    one can see what lanes and green fields and gardens still lay be-
                    tween the village and London, more than a mile away. Nursery
                    gardens, wide open spaces, brick kilns on Campden Hill, and gravel
                    pits. In the midst of green fields stood three or four houses called
                    "Bays Watering." The Serpentine was called the New River,
                    Kensington Gore consisted of five houses. Hogmore Lane and
                    Lobb's Field ran from the high-road towards Chelsea. Though I
                    have the map before me, I can hardly feel that it was ever true, and
                    yet I remember Hogmore Lane. And there was Love Lane beyond,
                    along which we used to go for straggling walks with our playfellows
                    the.Coles, who lived in the Terrace close by. We used to start about
                    six o'clock on summer mornings, and come home with 'branches of
                    hawthorn flowers to decorate our school-room and to remind our-
                    selves that it was May-time. 
                </note>
   <note xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" style="; " id="note_004">
      <hi id="idp756160" style="vertical-align: super;">*</hi> 4th December, 1794.</note>
   <note xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" style="; " id="note_003">
      <hi id="idp1039232" style="vertical-align: super;">*</hi> I like better to think of George Sand as I never saw her, with
gray hairs and a softened life, outcoming and helpful, and living in
later years among her plants and her grandchildren and her poor
people; to imagine her as I have heard her described in her age, 
                    <add id="idp1040192" style="font-style: italic;" type="editorial" resp="#mdalmau">[con't on p.202]</add> 
                    beneficent, occupied, tending and prescribing, distributing the simples 
out of her garden, healing the sick, softened by time, giving to
others day by day what she had earned by her nights of persistent
work.</note>
</notes>